<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Remote Roast</title>
    <description>Rating Twin Cities coffee shops for remote work.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 14:41:58 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 14:41:58 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spring Round Up 1</title>
        <description>&lt;h2&gt;A little recap of the first half of spring!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We started rating coffee shops at the start of Spring this year and we&apos;ve been having a great time doing it! But we know your time is precious and you may not have time to read them all, so we&apos;ve rounded them up for you in a nice little package. We&apos;ll give you the quick view (The Shots) if you&apos;ve only got a minute, but keep reading for some insights (Spilling the Beans) on where we went and how we felt about it. Yes, the headers are bad coffee puns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Shots&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:70%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Shop&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;City&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Stars&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi speed&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for meetings?&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/quixotic&quot;&gt;Quixotic Coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/hUHF1vepUCafYfnd7&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;St Paul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;rating-holder&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;c-rating c-rating--regular&quot; data-rating-value=&quot;5&quot;&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;1&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;2&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;3&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;4&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;5&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$2.75&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/skcoffee&quot;&gt;SK Coffee - Whittier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/2VnxBXBxqiLCMiUe6&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;
       &lt;div class=&quot;rating-holder&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;c-rating c-rating--regular&quot; data-rating-value=&quot;4&quot;&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;1&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;2&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;3&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;4&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;5&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;410&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maybe&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.50&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/corner-coffee-uptown&quot;&gt;Corner Coffee Uptown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/kbAe9j9VgzNmC6aw7&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Minneapolis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;
       &lt;div class=&quot;rating-holder&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;c-rating c-rating--regular&quot; data-rating-value=&quot;4.5&quot;&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;1&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;2&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;3&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;4&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;5&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;110&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$2.75&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/dogwood-saint-paul&quot;&gt;Dogwood Coffee - St Paul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/kbAe9j9VgzNmC6aw7&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;St Paul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;rating-holder&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;c-rating c-rating--regular&quot; data-rating-value=&quot;3.5&quot;&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;1&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;2&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;3&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;4&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;5&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;78&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.25&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/ninas&quot;&gt;Nina&apos;s Coffee Cafe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/Veo7SdX2p3hf5uPC8&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;St Paul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;
        &lt;div class=&quot;rating-holder&quot;&gt;
            &lt;div class=&quot;c-rating c-rating--regular&quot; data-rating-value=&quot;3.5&quot;&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;1&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;2&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;3&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;4&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;button&gt;5&lt;/button&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;46&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;No&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.00&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Spilling the Beans&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Quixotic Coffee&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We started our journey back in March with &lt;a href=&quot;/quixotic&quot;&gt;Quixotic Coffee&lt;/a&gt;. Quixotic was the coffee shop where Juliet first started working regularly after having frequented it in college. 
  It&apos;s comfortable, great for meetings, and they have a lot of tasty food options. Here&apos;s what we like most:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of booths! You can have your own personal space while still experiencing the vibrant coffee shop environment.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Osmar&apos;s favorite blueberry muffin can be found here (if he hasn&apos;t eaten them all).&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quixotic now has great smoothie and yogurt bowls.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It&apos;s easy to find parking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;SK Coffee - Whittier&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href=&quot;/skcoffee&quot;&gt;SK Coffee - Whittier&lt;/a&gt; opened up just a few blocks away from our house, we knew we&apos;d have to check it out.
Someone had to do the community the service of quality checking the new coffee spot and we selflessly volunteered to try their drinks and food. Here&apos;s what we thought about it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We&apos;re big fans of the matcha lattes at SK.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The food is top notch! They have a great lentil curry pastry that Juliet would like to eat daily.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Taking meetings at SK can be hit or miss. The music is usually at a decent level but sometimes is less suitable as the background to your Zoom call.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SK only has 21 seats so it&apos;s often close to full. Get there early to make sure you can sit! It&apos;s worth it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Corner Coffee - Uptown&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/corner-coffee-uptown&quot;&gt;Corner Coffee&lt;/a&gt; was one of the first places that we regularly worked at after moving to Uptown.
There&apos;s always a place to sit, the environment is laid back but still vibrant, and the baristas will get to know you if you show up often. Some key points:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Corner Coffee always has reliable wifi and lots of outlets making it great for meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The breakfast and lunch sandwiches are great and are made to order.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Get it while you can! The seasonal drinks are always a hit. We LOVE the Lavender Lemon Brew.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you need non-coffee options, Corner Coffee has got you covered with a variety of teas and other drinks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Dogwood Coffee - St Paul&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href=&quot;/dogwood-saint-paul&quot;&gt;Dogwood Coffee - St Paul&lt;/a&gt; was not one of our favorite remote work spots, it still earned itself a 3.5 star rating.
Although we like their coffee, the food options are lacking and the environment is somewhat uninspiring. I&apos;m running out of ways to introduce lists:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dogwood has great coffee. If you like to brew at home, it&apos;s worth picking up a bag of beans.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;While the food they have is good, there are very few options and their sandwiches sell out quickly leaving not many options for a meal.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you&apos;re looking for a non-distracting environment, Dogwood is a great choice!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There is pretty solid wifi and there has always been ample seating available when we have gone to Dogwood.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Nina&apos;s Coffee Cafe&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We love &lt;a href=&quot;/ninas&quot;&gt;Nina&apos;s Coffee Cafe&lt;/a&gt;. But maybe not for remote work. It&apos;s a fun spot with great drinks, however, it may be too distracting and there aren&apos;t many outlets. 
You can decide for yourself based on our quick notes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The ambiance at Nina&apos;s is great! While it may not be the best for work, it&apos;s a great social spot.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The food is pretty good but we&apos;ve had better pastries elsewhere. Not bad, just not the best.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Lots of dairy free milks at Nina&apos;s but beware - the drinks with caramel made Osmar&apos;s tummy hurt.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Because it&apos;s such a fun spot with great drinks, it&apos;s often fairly crowded which makes it a bit ofa riskier option.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s what we&apos;ve got, folks! Stick around for more reviews and round ups, and check out our new &lt;a href=&quot;/tldr&quot;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/a&gt; page if you hate our writing and just want the facts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/spring-roundup-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/spring-roundup-1/</guid>
        
        <category>roundup</category>
        
        
        <category>2023</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nina&apos;s Coffee Cafe</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Time for a history lesson folx&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bonus points if y&apos;all catch the theme of the section headings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;rumours-who-is-nina&quot;&gt;Rumours: Who is Nina?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nina&apos;s cafe coffeeshop is named after the founder &lt;a href=&quot;https://original.newsbreak.com/@the-streets-of-st-paul-1587459/2914482884419-nina-clifford-1848-1929&quot;&gt; Nina Clifford&lt;/a&gt;– whose real name is Hannah Steinbrecher. Born in Canada, Nina arrived in St. Paul in 1885, and her options of making a living wage were limited as a widow. But folx, that did not hold her back. She established a cafe and bought two other buildings– which no longer stand today– in the red light district of St. Paul. Nina&apos;s cafe was rumoured to be a brothel back in the day, but it was actually at those other locations where she ran that business. Of course, gossip doesn&apos;t stop there. Some of you may have even heard of those tunnels that supposedly run under Nina&apos;s cafe. Well, sadly these tunnels &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.joyinminnesota.com/home/the-myth-of-ninas-coffee-cafe&quot;&gt;do not actually exist (or so they say).&lt;/a&gt; Finally, the last thing I&apos;ll clear up is that yes, it is indeed pronounced NINE-uhs and not KNEE-nahs. RIP to all of you that corrected me over the past few years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;mystery-to-me-where-the-heck-is-the-bathroom&quot;&gt;Mystery to me: Where the heck is the bathroom?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nina&apos;s cafe is in a beautiful building that is only more breathtaking on the inside. The high ceilings and abundant natural light always puts me in a good mood. There is also plenty of seating and it&apos;s quite diverse: from couches to nooks and tables. That being said, it is a popular place and it does tend to be crowded. Regarding the bathrooms, there is only one, but it has been out of order the past few times. But no need to fear my fellow sensitive tummy folx as there are two backup bathrooms in Blair&apos;s Arcade– the building connected to Nina&apos;s. The only issue is... finding them can be a bit of a hassle, but Juliet and I have done it and are here to do the work so that you don&apos;t have to!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions to Narnia: alright, you&apos;re going to want to step outside the side door into the main hallway and take a right (if you take a left, you will be exiting the building, so uh don&apos;t do that). Walk down that mirror hallway past the hair salon and the fountains. Once you step foot on the carpet, you&apos;re going to want to go just a bit further until you see the first hallway to the left. Turn left into it and then left again at the end. There, you will see two doors with the lockpads and all that&apos;s left to do is punch it in and lock the door behind you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;46&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;91&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;64&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;90%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1?&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;mirage-are-you-actually-working&quot;&gt;Mirage: Are you actually working?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Nina&apos;s Cafe is a really nice spot to be in and fulfill your desire for a coffeshop work aesthetic, it may not be the best place if you really need to focus. If you&apos;re like me and are easily distracted, you are better off bringing some noise cancellation headphones and doing work that does not require all of your attention. It is usually pretty full, so there is always quite a bit going on. I would not take a meeting here nor would I come here if I had a lot of reading to get done. Nina&apos;s cafe is still a great place to have a fun drink and catch up with a friend. They also have a free parking lot nearby!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Some&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Distracting&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;No&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;the-dance-to-eat-or-not-to-eat&quot;&gt;The Dance: To eat or not to eat&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The coffee at Nina&apos;s is pretty decent (so Juliet tells me) and they have a few fun, and really good, teas. They have a few seasonal drinks that are always fun and I would definitely recommend. They also have a few dairy-free milks and we love having options. Here is some coffee data:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.00&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; While the food at Nina&apos;s isn&apos;t terrible, it was not my favorite. I&apos;ve only tried three different pastries and was not in love with any of them nor would I have them again. They also have a breakfast burrito and quiche that I may be trying sometime in the near future, because I will definitely be coming back to Nina&apos;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Pro tip&lt;/i&gt;: some drinks made with caramel have quite a bit of dairy in them. Even with a dairy-free milk, I would caution my lactose-unfriendly peeps to stay clear of them no matter how good they are :( &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/ninas/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/ninas/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>3.5 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>St Paul</category>
        
        <category>Summit-University</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dogwood Coffee - Saint Paul</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Woof woof&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just kidding. This review isn&apos;t about dogs. Tricked ya!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;when-its-too-ruff-to-work-from-home-get-some-coffee&quot;&gt;When it’s too &lt;em&gt;ruff&lt;/em&gt; to work from home, get some coffee!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, I am going to make puns. Stop reading now if you hate sophisticated humor. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had been to Dogwood a number of times before trying it out as a remote work spot. I had brewed their coffee at home and had some college homework sessions at a couple of their locations. But the first time I went to Dogwood&apos;s Saint Paul location for remote work was actually because I couldn&apos;t find a seat at &lt;a href=&quot;https://remoteroast.github.io/quixotic/&quot;&gt;Quixotic.&lt;/a&gt; That was the first time I went somewhere new to work where I didn&apos;t know if I could rely on the wifi. I wished at that time that there was a website where I could see which coffee shops were good for remote work. And now, here we are!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucky for me, the wifi was enough for my Zoom call, there was a place to sit, and I could get a good coffee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;78&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;86&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;49&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;40%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;is-it-affurdable&quot;&gt;Is it af&lt;em&gt;fur&lt;/em&gt;dable?&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dogwood roasts their own beans. I often buy them for my own brewing at home, so it&apos;s no surprise I like their coffee. But for those of you whose red flag is not drinking coffee, there are other drinks like hot teas, tea lattes, and golden milk. I particularly like their chai. Dogwood also has good seasonal drinks and a couple of dairy free options. And while the prices are not the cheapest of the coffee shops we&apos;ve collected data on, they&apos;re not the most expensive either.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.25&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.95&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;bone-appetit&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bone&lt;/em&gt; Appetit&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When considering all of the great food we&apos;ve had at coffee shops, I&apos;d say the food at dogwood is fine. I&apos;m not particularly excited by it and there are not many options besides pastries, but what they do have is good. They have a couple of sandwiches but they sell out quickly. The other meal-type option is oatmeal which is just fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Pastries&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;howl-is-the-work-environment&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Howl&lt;/em&gt; is the work environment?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as the work environment goes, Dogwood has a low key, non-distracting ambiance that is well suited for focusing on work and is great for taking calls. There are booths to silo yourself from the rest of the patrons. Or, if you&apos;re feeling social, there are tables that seat larger groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re easily distracted, Dogwood in Saint Paul may be a good spot for you. The music isn&apos;t too loud, there is not typically a big crowd, and there are not many distractions on the walls. There is not a lot of decor and the booths are all wood, so there is a bit of an echo since there isn&apos;t much around to absorb sound. Still, the environment is comfortable and it is a good place to get focused work done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Mellow&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, Dogwood Coffee in Saint Paul is a solid option. While it&apos;s not one of our top choices, that&apos;s not because it has any problems. There&apos;s a lot we like about it - including that it has a parking lot - but we give it a 3.5. Which, if you&apos;re data nerds like us, you&apos;ll recognize as being above average.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Pro tip&lt;/i&gt;: Grab a bag of beans! I&apos;m a fan of their light roasts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dogwood-saint-paul/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/dogwood-saint-paul/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>3.5 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>St Paul</category>
        
        <category>Saint Anthony Park</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Corner Coffee Uptown</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Where it all began...&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Osmar and I started working from (not) home together, Corner Coffee was our go to spot. It was near our house, it had a good energy, and most importantly -- it had a parking lot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;whats-so-good-about-working-from-corner-coffee&quot;&gt;What’s so good about working from Corner Coffee?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ironically located one door down from the corner of Hennepin and 28th, Corner Coffee has an ideal working environment that accommodates many working styles. Want to be comfy and chill out while you work? They have couches and warm seasonal drinks. Working with a group? There are long tables with lots of seating. Need privacy for a meeting? There&apos;s a room with a sliding door so you can shut yourself in like the antisocial hermit you are. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to all of that, there are not one but &lt;i&gt;TWO&lt;/i&gt; bathrooms, strong wifi, and there is always a place to sit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;110&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;86&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;14&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;51&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Osmar and I both have ~sensitive tummies~ which means we can&apos;t always drink coffee and sometimes milk translates to loss of integrity as we make our 10th trip to the bathroom in the hour...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;but-whether-or-not-we-can-have-caffeine&quot;&gt;But whether or not we can have caffeine…&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corner Coffee has great seasonal drinks for coffee lovers and h8rs alike! Personal favorites include the Chaider and the Lavender Lemon Cold Brew. They also have great hot and cold teas, as well as your classic coffee and espresso drinks. And, if you like the smell of coffee, Corner Coffee also roasts beans in house and while the fire alarm did go off one time, usually it just fills the room with the smell of fresh beans (the coffee kind).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; If you read the seasonal drinks and rolled your eyes at the concoctions because you&apos;re too cool to admit that coffee can taste good with additions other than cream and sugar, here are the simple stats for you bean water aficionados:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$2.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing we have come to appreciate at Corner Coffee are the baristas! Everyone made an effort to learn our names, know our drink preferences, and they always say hi. They also frequently will bring food and drinks right to where we&apos;re sitting. As a former barista at a fast paced coffee shop named after a reindeer, I know that&apos;s not always what you want to do. But I take that as a sign that they like what they&apos;re doing and the environment they work in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;sammies-galore&quot;&gt;Sammies galore!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you&apos;re so busy that you rush out the door, go-gurt in hand, and when you get to the coffee shop, all you can think about is food. Only me with the go-gurt? That&apos;s fine because Corner Coffee has something better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Open your nostrils folks, because Corner Coffee has delicious breakfast sandwiches made to order and when you smell that bacon, you may just order one yourself. We&apos;re also big fans of the BLT. They do have bacon-less options too -- shout out to my Kosher cousins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;oh-shit-my-computer-is-about-to-die&quot;&gt;Oh shit, my computer is about to die!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you caught yourself saying that before? Don&apos;t fear! An outlet is near! Corner Coffee is very well suited for remote work with outlets along every wall and a chill work environment. The music is usually at a reasonable volume, many of the people inside are also working, and it&apos;s easy and comfortable to take a meeting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s what we&apos;ve got for Corner Coffee!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Pro tip&lt;/i&gt;: Are you a big tea drinker but the tea gets cold before you can finish it? You can get the whole pitcher at Corner Coffee and pour it yourself! It stays nice and steamy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/corner-coffee-uptown/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/corner-coffee-uptown/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>4.5 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>Minneapolis</category>
        
        <category>Uptown</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SK Coffee</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;New coffee shop alert!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone living in Uptown knows the clusterf*ck that driving and parking can be. Sometimes, the last thing you need on a Monday morning is to deal with, well, anything. That’s why we decided to walk to a nearby coffee shop that recently opened up on 24th and Lyndale: SK Coffee!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;lets-set-the-stage&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Let’s set the stage&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Located on Lyndale where Misfit Coffee once stood, this coffee shop’s atmosphere is welcoming to both hipsters and young professionals alike without that hint of snobbiness. I love the pops of color against the white and the wall of plants. The high ceilings and wall-length windows makes it a very bright, open space. They also have a beautiful couch surrounded by plants, and who doesn’t love a couch for those dreadful Monday mornings during which your video and microphone are always off? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;410&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;83.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50-80%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During that latest winter storm, neither Juliet nor I had the bravery to take either of our cars out (not because we refused to shovel and deeply regretted it soon after) and walked to SK for a whole week. Since then, we have become regulars at the expense of our budgets, and here’s a few reasons why:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;a-matcha-made-in-heaven-i-rolled-my-eyes-too&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;A matcha made in heaven (I rolled my eyes too)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During yet another short-lived phase of swearing off coffee, I started buying matcha at any place I could get my hands on it. I can say without a doubt that my favorite place to get it is– you guessed it– SK Coffee. I typically order the classic vanilla oatmilk matcha latte (yes, unapologetically dairy-free… most times … sometimes.. if you know, you know). I didn’t realize until a few matchas in that it had galium and not vanilla. Through that conversation I learned about their partnership with  &lt;a href=&quot;https://mspmag.com/eat-and-drink/3leche-it-s-all-in-the-mix/&quot;&gt; 3Leche &lt;/a&gt;. 3Leche are a group of three mixologists and bartenders that specialize in fermentation and have been expanding to non-alcoholic beverages such as coffee. SK coffee also carries their dolce de leche syrup, which I have not tried yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; And yes, since this is a coffee blog, I guess I should talk about coffee. Here’s the bean juice stats for all you caffeine addicts!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Few&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The staff are also one of the best features of SK. As a chaotic person who’s always on the go and frequently forgets to feed himself, I have had a few occasions where I asked the staff to list out their pastries (sorry for being that person). They are very nice about it and make the ordering anxiety bearable. Oh! The food! It definitely deserves its own mini heading:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;pecans-lentils-and-cheese&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pecans, lentils, and cheese&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know, you’re probably like &lt;i&gt; what the heck &lt;/i&gt; but don’t worry those ingredients can all be found in separate pastries. But wow their pecan bear claw is truly divine. The only thing more splendid than that– if you’re in a ~savory~ mood– is their lentils pastry. Trust me, as a kid who was forced to eat lentil soup and still has nightmares about it, the lentils in this hot-pocket-like pastry (idk, I don’t bake, but I’m sure Juliet knows what it’s called so you could ask via comments) are WORTH it. I haven’t had one of their cheese croissants because I’m trying to be better about being dairy-free. However, my fellow lactose-intolerant folx know that will not last long especially with the quality of these pastries. (Wow, I’m really hungry right now and realizing I forgot to eat dinner). Anyways, it feels weird to not have a data table follow this so I’m just going to casually drop one now: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Few&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;working-from-sk-coffee&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Working from SK Coffee&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last section, I promise. If you’ve stuck with me this far, then I commend you for having a better attention span than I do. But, in the words of queen Rihanna herself, THIS is what you came forrrr (unless you’re one of my friends being forced to read this)...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maybe&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The table speaks for itself, but I will add...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt; I’m slightly more picky than Juliet about where I take meetings, but to be fair I rarely have any. &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt; The staff is allowed to play their own tunes, and while I personally am an occasional fan of screamo/light metal, it was funny to see Juliet taking a meeting with that as background music. I should point out this has only happened once!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, local coffee shop, good vibes. Will definitely keep working from here and might venture to their St. Paul location which I only recently found out about. Stable wifi and good drinks. Juliet and I both give it a 4/5 and would definitely recommend it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;i&gt;Pro tip&lt;/i&gt;: SK is also a roastery! If you end up becoming obsessed like us, they have &lt;a href=&quot;https://skcoffeeplease.com/subscription&quot;&gt; subscription plans &lt;/a&gt; for delivering coffee beans to your door. &lt;i&gt;Sigh&lt;/i&gt;, if only they delivered the matcha.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/skcoffee/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/skcoffee/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>4 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>Minneapolis</category>
        
        <category>Whittier</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quixotic Coffee</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Our first review!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the winter of 2021, in the midst of roommate drama and quarantine induced insanity, I decided I needed to get away from my desk in the basement and find someplace else to work. Quixotic was the first place I went. I was truly a modern woman as I traveled all the way from Minneapolis to St Paul, finally exercising the vast freedom of movement I had as a remote worker. I finally understood &quot;van life&quot; and the &quot;digital nomad&quot; mentality. I mean, I was working from a completely different city!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, that might be a stretch. It was Saint Paul, not Costa Rica. But still, there was a sense of excitement and freedom working from neither an office, nor my desk at home. Quixotic was the start to my &quot;work from anywhere&quot; journey and what a great place it was to start with. All that said, you&apos;re not here for my trip down memory lane. You&apos;re here for the data, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;so-onto-the-bean-juicy-stuff&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;So onto the (bean) juicy stuff&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll start with our basic quantitative metrics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;78&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;27&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;48&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50-80%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose Quixotic to launch my coffee-shop-remote-woman-in-STEM (god that&apos;s obnoxious) adventure because it felt comfortable and familiar. I had done homework there as a college student and what I loved - and still love - most about it is that there are several booths with tall wooden walls between them. You can be in your own personal work area while still participating in the vibrant energy of a neighborhood coffee shop. Not only that, but each table has an outlet and the wifi is reliable, so you can take Zoom calls without worrying about a dying battery or losing connection. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In addition to the booths, there is a larger closed off conference room that can be reserved if you want to work with friends or co-workers. They also have bar seating and regular tables if all of the booths are taken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;but-enough-about-tables-i-know-you-want-to-hear-about-the-coffee&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;But enough about tables. I know you want to hear about the coffee…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$2.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you just finished a stressful meeting with the boss man or you just got a raise and you deserve a little reward, Quixotic has fun and tasty seasonal drinks that you&apos;ll end up spending all of your money on every day for several weeks until you feel bad about it but still can&apos;t stop...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucky for you, they also have really good drip coffee at a very reasonable price! If coffee&apos;s not your thing, there is a variety of teas, kombuchas, tea lattes, smoothies, and juices to choose from. Personally, I am a fan of their matcha as well as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jinxtea.com/about&quot;&gt; Jinx teas &lt;/a&gt;they offer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;onto-the-food&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Onto the food…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re anything like me, having coffee on an empty stomach will send you racing to the bathroom. And one bathroom in a coffee shop with 48 seats (yes, we counted) can be a big risk. But at Quixotic, you can find a variety of fresh pastries from &lt;a href=&quot;http://patisserie46.com/&quot;&gt;Patisserie 46&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://siftglutenfree.com/&quot;&gt; Sift&lt;/a&gt; (gluten free!), and more recently they&apos;ve added smoothie and yogurt bowls from  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/bomdiatreats/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Bom Dia Treats&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;finally-onto-the-work-metrics-that-are-mostly-biased-and-completely-subjective&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Finally onto the “work metrics” that are mostly biased and completely subjective…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The work environment at Quixotic is fantastic. Most of the people there are working on something, whether it&apos;s school work or &quot;work work&quot; - whatever that means. For someone trying to dip their toes into the coffee shop work life, Quixotic is a great place to test out, especially if you can sit in a booth. Can you tell I love the booths?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music is usually at a comfortable volume, people are generally respectful of their noise levels, and the food and coffee are reliably good. You don&apos;t have to worry about your wifi cutting out or the background noise being so loud your co-workers can&apos;t hear you in a meeting, and they don&apos;t unexpectedly start playing niche hard-core bands (more on that in another review).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, Quixotic is a great place for a remote worker. Osmar gives it a 4.5/5, but I give it a 5/5 and this is my review so what I say goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pro tip: If you can’t find street parking, pull into the alley just north of the shop. There’s 2 hour parking along one side. But leave a spot for us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/quixotic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quixotic/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>5 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>St Paul</category>
        
        <category>Highland Park</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Remote Roast!</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Do you work remotely? Trying to find good coffee shops to work at? You&apos;ve come to the right place!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the age of remote work, it can be easy to get stuck in your house. But when we decided to come together and work at local coffee shops, we had to search around for places with good wifi, comfortable work environments, and prices that wouldn&apos;t break the bank. We wanted to know which places were good for meetings. Where could we go for fun seasonal drinks when we wanted a little treat? If we were staying for a while, did they have good food? And most importantly, with all the caffeine we were putting in our bodies -- how many bathrooms did they have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, data nerds that we are, we decided to put all of our findings in one place so you don&apos;t have to scour Yelp reviews to see if the wifi is fast enough to load TikTok on your breaks from hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Who are we?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;image-txt-container&quot;&gt;
 &lt;img class=&quot;author-thumb-large&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/osmar.png&quot; alt=&quot;Osmar&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;a&gt;After dropping out of bartending school, Osmar is now a computational neuroscience researcher at the University of Minnesota. His favorite espresso drink is an iced vanilla americano (light ice), and he&apos;s also a big fan of iced chai and london fog lattes. When not at a coffee shop, he can be found setting off fires in kitchens. Despite being incredibly chaotic in the kitchen, he does make mean shrimp stew. &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;image-txt-container&quot;&gt;
   &lt;img class=&quot;author-thumb-large&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/juliet.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Juliet&quot; /&gt;  
 &lt;a&gt;After four years as a barista at a Minnesota coffee chain that shall not be named, Juliet is now a Data Analyst at the Star Tribune. Her favorite espresso drink is a hot americano with not too much water, but she also loves a plain old coffee or a fun flavored latte every once in a while. Juliet also plays in Twin Cities band Good Luck Alaska that is working on their debut EP. &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-how-are-we-doing-this-thing&quot;&gt;So how are we doing this thing?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;like-any-good-scientists-we-have-a-rigorous-methodology-kind-of&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like any good scientists, we have a rigorous methodology… kind of&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most food critics keep their identities hidden. They return to a restaurant multiple times to taste everything on the menu. They get a well rounded view of the different menu items, the atmosphere and service, all while remaining anonymous so that the service they receive is not skewed.
&lt;br /&gt;
Unfortunately for us (and for you), we can’t afford every menu item. But on the plus side, we’re a couple of nobody Zillennials, so we fly by under the radar unrecognizable to baristas worldwide.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;but-onto-the-good-stuff&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;But onto the good stuff…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be measuring and collecting a variety of data points about each coffee shop – some objective, some not – and sharing them with you. Here’s a look at some of our quantitative data (that’s nerd speak for numbers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;410&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;83.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;30%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll accompany that data with illustrative descriptions like:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;The millennial pink bathroom has all the amenities a girl could dream of. Nobody judged us for going in and out every 20 minutes.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Next, we’ll get more into the coffee, sharing both quantitative (you know what that means now) with qualitative (read: words/categories) data points:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Few&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These too will have pretentious descriptions like:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;Juliet sipped on an espresso tonic with flavor notes of stone fruit and bullshit. Osmar opted for a matcha latte and questioned whether the milk was dairy or his preferred alternative until the last drop hit his colon.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;then-the-food&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then the food…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;and-the-work-metrics&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;And the “work metrics”…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maybe&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get the point.
&lt;br /&gt;
We aim to review a new coffee shop every week and let you know what we think. Key word there is “aim”. We’re not perfect, but we’ll let you know which coffee shops are.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Welcome/</guid>
        
        <category>methodology</category>
        
        
        <category>Minneapolis</category>
        
        <category>About</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
