<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Remote Roast</title>
    <description>Rating Twin Cities coffee shops for remote work.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:55:15 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 21:55:15 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.3.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quixotic Coffee</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Our first review!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the winter of 2021, in the midst of roommate drama and quarantine induced insanity, I decided I needed to get away from my desk in the basement and find someplace else to work. Quixotic was the first place I went. I was truly a modern woman as I traveled all the way from Minneapolis to St Paul, finally exercising the vast freedom of movement I had as a remote worker. I finally understood &quot;van life&quot; and the &quot;digital nomad&quot; mentality. I mean, I was working from a completely different city!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Okay, that might be a stretch. It was Saint Paul, not Costa Rica. But still, there was a sense of excitement and freedom working from neither an office, nor my desk at home. Quixotic was the start to my &quot;work from anywhere&quot; journey and what a great place it was to start with. All that said, you&apos;re not here for my trip down memory lane. You&apos;re here for the data, right?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;so-onto-the-bean-juicy-stuff&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;So onto the (bean) juicy stuff&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll start with our basic quantitative metrics:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;120&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;78&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;27&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;48&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;50-80%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose Quixotic to launch my coffee-shop-remote-woman-in-STEM (god that&apos;s obnoxious) adventure because it felt comfortable and familiar. I had done homework there as a college student and what I loved - and still love - most about it is that there are several booths with tall wooden walls between them. You can be in your own personal work area while still participating in the vibrant energy of a neighborhood coffee shop. Not only that, but each table has an outlet and the wifi is reliable, so you can take Zoom calls without worrying about a dying battery or losing connection. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; In addition to the booths, there is a larger closed off conference room that can be reserved if you want to work with friends or co-workers. They also have bar seating and regular tables if all of the booths are taken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;but-enough-about-tables-i-know-you-want-to-hear-about-the-coffee&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;But enough about tables. I know you want to hear about the coffee…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$2.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.75&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you just finished a stressful meeting with the boss man or you just got a raise and you deserve a little reward, Quixotic has fun and tasty seasonal drinks that you&apos;ll end up spending all of your money on every day for several weeks until you feel bad about it but still can&apos;t stop...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lucky for you, they also have really good drip coffee at a very reasonable price! If coffee&apos;s not your thing, there is a variety of teas, kombuchas, tea lattes, smoothies, and juices to choose from. Personally, I am a fan of their matcha as well as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.jinxtea.com/about&quot;&gt; Jinx teas &lt;/a&gt;they offer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;onto-the-food&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Onto the food…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&apos;re anything like me, having coffee on an empty stomach will send you racing to the bathroom. And one bathroom in a coffee shop with 48 seats (yes, we counted) can be a big risk. But at Quixotic, you can find a variety of fresh pastries from &lt;a href=&quot;http://patisserie46.com/&quot;&gt;Patisserie 46&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://siftglutenfree.com/&quot;&gt; Sift&lt;/a&gt; (gluten free!), and more recently they&apos;ve added smoothie and yogurt bowls from  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/bomdiatreats/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Bom Dia Treats&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;finally-onto-the-work-metrics-that-are-mostly-biased-and-completely-subjective&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Finally onto the “work metrics” that are mostly biased and completely subjective…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The work environment at Quixotic is fantastic. Most of the people there are working on something, whether it&apos;s school work or &quot;work work&quot; - whatever that means. For someone trying to dip their toes into the coffee shop work life, Quixotic is a great place to test out, especially if you can sit in a booth. Can you tell I love the booths?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The music is usually at a comfortable volume, people are generally respectful of their noise levels, and the food and coffee are reliably good. You don&apos;t have to worry about your wifi cutting out or the background noise being so loud your co-workers can&apos;t hear you in a meeting, and they don&apos;t unexpectedly start playing niche hard-core bands (more on that in another review).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, Quixotic is a great place for a remote worker. Osmar gives it a 4.5/5, but I give it a 5/5 and this is my review so what I say goes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Pro tip: If you can’t find street parking, pull into the alley just north of the shop. There’s 2 hour parking along one side. But leave a spot for us!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/quixotic/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/quixotic/</guid>
        
        <category>review</category>
        
        <category>5 stars</category>
        
        
        <category>St Paul</category>
        
        <category>Highland Park</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Remote Roast!</title>
        <description>&lt;h4&gt;Do you work remotely? Trying to find good coffee shops to work at? You&apos;ve come to the right place!&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the age of remote work, it can be easy to get stuck in your house. But when we decided to come together and work at local coffee shops, we had to search around for places with good wifi, comfortable work environments, and prices that wouldn&apos;t break the bank. We wanted to know which places were good for meetings. Where could we go for fun seasonal drinks when we wanted a little treat? If we were staying for a while, did they have good food? And most importantly, with all the caffeine we were putting in our bodies -- how many bathrooms did they have?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, data nerds that we are, we decided to put all of our findings in one place so you don&apos;t have to scour Yelp reviews to see if the wifi is fast enough to load TikTok on your breaks from hard work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Who are we?&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;image-txt-container&quot;&gt;
 &lt;img class=&quot;author-thumb-large&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/osmar.png&quot; alt=&quot;Osmar&quot; /&gt; 
 &lt;a&gt;After dropping out of bartending school, Osmar is now a computational neuroscience researcher at the University of Minnesota. His favorite espresso drink is an iced vanilla americano (light ice), and he&apos;s also a big fan of iced chai and london fog lattes. When not at a coffee shop, he can be found setting off fires in kitchens. Despite being incredibly chaotic in the kitchen, he does make mean shrimp stew. &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;image-txt-container&quot;&gt;
   &lt;img class=&quot;author-thumb-large&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/juliet.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Juliet&quot; /&gt;  
 &lt;a&gt;After four years as a barista at a Minnesota coffee chain that shall not be named, Juliet is now a Data Analyst at the Star Tribune. Her favorite espresso drink is a hot americano with not too much water, but she also loves a plain old coffee or a fun flavored latte every once in a while. Juliet also plays in Twin Cities band Good Luck Alaska that is working on their debut EP. &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;so-how-are-we-doing-this-thing&quot;&gt;So how are we doing this thing?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;like-any-good-scientists-we-have-a-rigorous-methodology-kind-of&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Like any good scientists, we have a rigorous methodology… kind of&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most food critics keep their identities hidden. They return to a restaurant multiple times to taste everything on the menu. They get a well rounded view of the different menu items, the atmosphere and service, all while remaining anonymous so that the service they receive is not skewed.
&lt;br /&gt;
Unfortunately for us (and for you), we can’t afford every menu item. But on the plus side, we’re a couple of nobody Zillennials, so we fly by under the radar unrecognizable to baristas worldwide.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;but-onto-the-good-stuff&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;But onto the good stuff…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ll be measuring and collecting a variety of data points about each coffee shop – some objective, some not – and sharing them with you. Here’s a look at some of our quantitative data (that’s nerd speak for numbers).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:85%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Wifi Speed (mbps)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Noise Level (dB)&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Tables&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Seats&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;% Crowded&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Bathrooms&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;410&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;83.5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;21&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;30%&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll accompany that data with illustrative descriptions like: 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;The millennial pink bathroom has all the amenities a girl could dream of. Nobody judged us for going in and out every 20 minutes.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Next, we’ll get more into the coffee, sharing both quantitative (you know what that means now) with qualitative (read: words/categories) data points:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Drip Coffee&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Coffee Taste&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;$ Small Latte&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;# Dairy-Free Milks&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Non Coffee Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Seasonal Drinks&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$3.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;$4.50&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Few&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Yes&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These too will have pretentious descriptions like:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;Juliet sipped on an espresso tonic with flavor notes of stone fruit and bullshit. Osmar opted for a matcha latte and questioned whether the milk was dairy or his preferred alternative until the last drop hit his colon.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;then-the-food&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Then the food…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Options&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Food Quality&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5 id=&quot;and-the-work-metrics&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;And the “work metrics”…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;table-responsive&quot; style=&quot;font-size:80%&quot;&gt;
  &lt;table class=&quot;table&quot;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Outlets&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Work Environment&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th scope=&quot;col&quot;&gt;Suitable for Meetings&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Many&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Chill&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;Maybe&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You get the point.
&lt;br /&gt;
We aim to review a new coffee shop every week and let you know what we think. Key word there is “aim”. We’re not perfect, but we’ll let you know which coffee shops are.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/Welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/Welcome/</guid>
        
        <category>data</category>
        
        <category>methodology</category>
        
        
        <category>Minneapolis</category>
        
        <category>About</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
